// use this quizData in your app.
export const quizData = [{
    "question": "Which of these albums is by The Weeknd?",
    "a": "Blonde",
    "b": "Ctrl",
    "c": "Thursday",
    "d": "Lemonade",
    "correct": "c",
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of Frank Ocean's critically acclaimed 2016 album?",
    "a": "Channel Orange",
    "b": "Blonde",
    "c": "Endless",
    "d": "nostalgia, ULTRA",
    "correct": "b",
},
{
    "question": "Which of these is a song by Beyoncé?",
    "a": "Good Days",
    "b": "Formation",
    "c": "Telepatía",
    "d": "Location",
    "correct": "b",
},
{
    "question": "What is the title of SZA's debut studio album?",
    "a": "Ctrl",
    "b": "SOS",
    "c": "Anti",
    "d": "Born to Die",
    "correct": "a",
},
{
    "question": "Which song brought Kali Uchis significant mainstream recognition?",
    "a": "Love Drought",
    "b": "10%",
    "c": "Telepatía",
    "d": "Lost",
    "correct": "c",
},
{
    "question": "Brent Faiyaz is known for his contribution to which genre?",
    "a": "R&B",
    "b": "Country",
    "c": "Pop",
    "d": "EDM",
    "correct": "a",
},
{
    "question": "Which artist collaborated with Daniel Caesar on the hit song 'Best Part'?",
    "a": "H.E.R.",
    "b": "SZA",
    "c": "Kali Uchis",
    "d": "Ariana Grande",
    "correct": "a",
},
{
    "question": "What is PinkPantheress known for?",
    "a": "Her acting career",
    "b": "Her lo-fi, bedroom pop music",
    "c": "Her work in fashion",
    "d": "Her jazz compositions",
    "correct": "b",
},
{
    "question": "Which of these songs is a hit by Frank Ocean?",
    "a": "Crew Love",
    "b": "Nights",
    "c": "Pray You Catch Me",
    "d": "Good Days",
    "correct": "b",
},
{
    "question": "Which Beyoncé album features the song 'Drunk in Love'?",
    "a": "4",
    "b": "B'Day",
    "c": "Lemonade",
    "d": "Beyoncé",
    "correct": "d",
},
{
    "question": "Which of these is a hit song by The Weeknd?",
    "a": "Thinkin Bout You",
    "b": "The Hills",
    "c": "All the Stars",
    "d": "Love Galore",
    "correct": "b",
},
{
    "question": "Which Kali Uchis song was featured on Tyler, The Creator's album 'Flower Boy'?",
    "a": "See You Again",
    "b": "Telepatía",
    "c": "Feel Like a Fool",
    "d": "Isolation",
    "correct": "a",
},
{
    "question": "What is the name of Brent Faiyaz's debut studio album?",
    "a": "Lost",
    "b": "F*** the World",
    "c": "Sonder Son",
    "d": "Wasteland",
    "correct": "c",
},
{
    "question": "Which SZA song became a viral hit on social media platforms?",
    "a": "Good Days",
    "b": "The Weekend",
    "c": "Love Galore",
    "d": "Broken Clocks",
    "correct": "a",
},
{
    "question": "Which song by Daniel Caesar features Kali Uchis?",
    "a": "Get You",
    "b": "Who Hurt You?",
    "c": "We Find Love",
    "d": "Streetcar",
    "correct": "a",
},
// you can add more quiz here
]
